/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data2_1', {
    title: '2.1 Rounding Whole Numbers',
    path: '2.1-rounding-whole-numbers',
    children: [{
        title: 'Rounding Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Round this whole number to the}}}{\\row{\\str{tens place: }}}{\\row{\\str{471}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{470}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\placevalue{471}{1}{showanswer}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Rounding Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Round this whole number to the}}}{\\row{\\str{thousands place: }}}{\\row{\\str{1346}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{1000}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\placevalue{1346}{3}{showanswer}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Rounding Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Round this whole number to the}}}{\\row{\\str{tens place: }}}{\\row{\\str{684}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{680}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\placevalue{684}{1}{showanswer}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Rounding Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Round this whole number to the}}}{\\row{\\str{tens place: }}}{\\row{\\str{959}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{960}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\placevalue{959}{1}{showanswer}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Rounding Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Round this whole number to the}}}{\\row{\\str{hundreds place: }}}{\\row{\\str{461}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{500}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\placevalue{461}{2}{showanswer}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Rounding Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Round this whole number to the}}}{\\row{\\str{ten thousands place: }}}{\\row{\\str{3990495}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{3990000}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\placevalue{3990495}{4}{showanswer}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Rounding Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Round this whole number to the}}}{\\row{\\str{ten thousands place: }}}{\\row{\\str{27523018}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{27520000}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\placevalue{27523018}{4}{showanswer}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Rounding Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Round this whole number to the}}}{\\row{\\str{hundred thousands place: }}}{\\row{\\str{563548}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{600000}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\placevalue{563548}{5}{showanswer}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Rounding Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Round this whole number to the}}}{\\row{\\str{tens place: }}}{\\row{\\str{230179}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{230180}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\placevalue{230179}{1}{showanswer}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Rounding Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Round this whole number to the}}}{\\row{\\str{hundreds place: }}}{\\row{\\str{49952}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{50000}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\placevalue{49952}{2}{showanswer}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }]
});
